Cohen and Tate is a crime, thriller, action film directed by Eric Red.
A boy kidnapped by two mismatched hitmen puts them at each other's throats
while being driven to their employers, possibly to be killed.
Cohen, an older professional becomes increasingly irritated with his partner Tate, a brutish killer, when
their prisoner uses unnatural guile and resourcefulness to play them off against each other.
Cohen, played by Roy Scheider.
Tate, played by Adam Baldwin.
Travis Knight, played by Harley Cross.
Jeff Knight, played by Cooper Huckabee.
Martha Knight, played by Suzanne Savoy.
FBI George, played by Marco Perella.
Cohen and Tate (also known as Cohen & Tate) is a 1989 American thriller film written and
directed by Eric Red and starring Roy Scheider, Adam Baldwin and Harley Cross.
It was Red's feature film debut.
The film is considered as a cinematic version of O.
Henry's short story "The Ransom of Red Chief".
The film explores themes of assassin, kidnapping,
texas, witness protection, houston, texas.
The tone is emotional and intense.